<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WindowsRecovery</string>
    <string name="wim_dir">/storage/sdcard0/tsing_recovery/test.wim</string>
    <string name="downloadaddress">#</string>
    <string name="total">General introduction: This APP mainly includes two interfaces: restore system and configuration information</string>
    <string name="recovery">Restore the system: the use of Microsofts official ESD files to achieve Windows system recovery, the main operations are:
    1. Click the Restore System button at the bottom of the screen to bring up the User Selection dialog box.; 
    2. Select the normal user;
    Warning: At this point can not carry out other operations - including shutdown and other dangerous action;
    After the progress is complete, the system is restored</string>
    <string name="setup">Configuration information, custom APP default information, the main operations are:
    1. wim file: the location of the custom input ESD file; 
    2. Download address: Custom input ESD file download URL;
    3. Command line: Execute shell command
    Click the "Save" button and store it in the configuration file</string>
    <string name="introduction1" >一、First, use the method \n</string>
    <string name="introduction11">1. Application scope</string>
    <string name="introduction111">\tThe tool will be in Yang days, Kai days and NEW THINKCENTRE models and pre-installed WINDOWS XP and WINDOWS7, WINDOWS8, WINDOWS8.1, WINDOWS10 non-Edu models with.</string>
    <string name="introduction12">2. Can I back up the WIN10 system?</string>
    <string name="introduction121">\tVersion 1.0 does not support WIN7 and the following.
    \t1.1 version began to support UEFI boot GPT partition WIN8, WIN8.1 and WIN10.</string>
    <string name="introduction13">3. u disk has no special requirements?</string>
    <string name="introduction131">\tU disk performance on the software experience a greater impact, priority USB3.0 recommended equipment. From the previous test results, the more high-end U disk, the better the performance and the effect, the backup speed block, start fast. 
	In addition, the size is also required. The software calculates a reasonable value based on the backup size, and the mobile device must be larger than the value to use.</string>
    <string name="introduction2" >二、Backup mechanism\n</string>
    <string name="introduction21" >\tWIM is an abbreviation for Microsoft Windows Imaging Format (WIM), which is a Windows file-based image format. The WIM image format also allows multiple images to be stored in an actual file. 
	The WIM image format also enables compression and a single instance, which greatly reduces the size of the image file. WIM, although similar to the Ghost way to install the system, but more flexible than Ghost, it allows us to restore the image file to the hard disk before, select the recovery partition, and other simple configuration.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recovery">RecoveryActivity</string>
    <string name="wechat">none</string>
    <string name="tip">Please select the system you want to restore</string>
    <string name="yes">Continue</string>
    <string name="no">Cancel</string>
    <string name="online">Online</string>
    <string name="offline">Local</string>
    <string name="left_bar">System</string>
    <string name="main_bar">Disk partition</string>
    <string name="help_info">help information</string>
    <string name="bt_dl">Windows Mirror download</string>
    <string name="bt_wim">Windows Mirror deployment</string>
    <string name="bt_efi">Windows EFI Backup</string>
    <string name="next_step">The next step</string>
</resources>
